jaspreet.work099@gmail.com

Jaspreet Singh Saini UX/UI Designer

+91 62674 38590

Indore, India

Career Objective

Creative UX/UI Designer with over 1.5+ years experience crafting beautiful Userfriendly Digital Experiences that make sense. I have a solid understanding of the design process. I am highly motivated and capable of working in a fast-paced environment. Looking for opportunities to learn and gain more exposure in this field.

Skills

User Interface & Experience Design, Wireframe, Prototype, Graphic Designing, Frontend Development, **Open Source Contribution**

Tools · Figma, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, VS Code, Git & GitHub

Soft Skills · Collaboration, Good Listener, Punctual, Good Observer, Creative Thinking, Work ethic, Networking

Experience

Indianpreneur · Magazine Designer Intern

June 2022 - September 2022

- · The first month of my internship I did research regarding the magazine design.
- · Then, I've started designing magazines, The first magazine is related to Top Influential Indianpreneurs and the one is based on EV Industry.
- In the short span of time, I designed two long magazines and gained lifetime experience on about Magazine Industry

Muniversiti EdCorp · Graphic Designing Intern

November 2021 - Feburary 2022

- The first month was a training period where I grasp so many different concepts using Figma & Adobe illustrator. After that, I started working on social media creatives.
- · Gradually, I was asked to make brochures, collaboration post designs and a lot of stuff. I have designed 7 to 8 brochures during my internship.
- During the last month, I studied more about UX/UI Designing

Medi-Caps University ACM Student Chapter • Assistant Graphics Head

March 2021 - August 2022

- Being a Newbie in college, I got a thick opportunity to showcase my skills. I was interviewed for Graphic Designing Executive Member. I got selected and was working their since March 2021
- I was promoted to Assistant Graphics Head in October 2021 after learning and creating more designs. I've worked with a team that's always eager to learn and do new things.
- I was responsible for the ideation and execution of social media posts, and I managed a team of up to three people

Education

Medi-Caps University • BCA

2020 - 2023

Currently a final-year student oscillating between internship and attendance with 9.2 CGPA.

Hobbies

Shooting Time-lapse, Creative photography and videography.

Portfolio Website LinkedIn GitHub **Behance**